(Sheldon:)I've come up with three ideas.
(Sheldon:)The first is a chance for her
(Sheldon:)to play the harp
with the L.A. Philharmonic.
(Penny:)Wow. You can really
arrange that?
(Sheldon:)Well, I said a chance,
you know.
(Sheldon:)When you tell them
it's your birthday
(Sheldon:)at Bennigan's,
they make a fuss.
(Sheldon:)I don't see why the Philharmonic
would be any different.
(Bernadette:)How about something
a little more realistic?
(Sheldon:)Well, Amy enjoys
knitting her own sweaters,
(Sheldon:)so I was thinking of getting her
an all-expense-paid trip
(Sheldon:)to the Wisconsin Sheep
and Wool Festival.
(Penny:)Sorry. I was waiting
for the bazinga.
(Bernadette:)Hold on. It could be romantic.
(Bernadette:)The two of them away together,
(Bernadette:)keeping each other warm
in snowy Wisconsin.
(Sheldon:)No, no, no, no.
She'd be going alone.
(Sheldon:)Well, if you think
I'm afraid of birds,
(Sheldon:)you should see me around sheep.
(Penny:)Okay, well,
what's the third option?
(Sheldon:)That I have coitus with her.
(glass shatters on floor)
(Leonard:)What do you think about giving
Sheldon's ticket to Stuart?
(Leonard:)I don't know.
(Raj:)Have you ever seen a movie
with Stuart before?